Donald Schein Papers
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- 1980, Budget and Finance Committee, nam_apap209-425 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- 1980, Community Advisory Board, 1980-1987; nam_apap209-426 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- 1980, Corporation for Public Broadcasting, 1980-1987; nam_apap209-427 (Box 15, Folder 11-12)
- 1980, Corporation for Public Broadcasting Computing and Telecommunication Planning Task Force Final Report, nam_apap209-428 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- 1980, CPB Meeting, 1980 July 15; nam_apap209-429 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- 1980, CPB Memoranda to Station Managers, nam_apap209-430 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- 1980, CPB Publications, nam_apap209-431 (Box 15, Folder 16-17)
- 1980, Current, Periodical, nam_apap209-432 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- 1980, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1980 January; nam_apap209-433 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- 1980, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1980 February; nam_apap209-434 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- 1980, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1980 March; nam_apap209-435 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- 1980, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1980 April; nam_apap209-436 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- 1980, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1980 May; nam_apap209-437 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- 1980, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1980 June; nam_apap209-438 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- 1980, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1980 July; nam_apap209-439 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- 1980, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1980 August; nam_apap209-440 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- 1980, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1980 September; nam_apap209-441 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- 1980, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1980 October; nam_apap209-442 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- 1980, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1980 November; nam_apap209-443 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- 1980, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1980 December; nam_apap209-444 (Box 15, Folder 30)
- 1980, Development Committee, nam_apap209-445 (Box 15, Folder 31)
- 1980, Endowment Committee, nam_apap209-446 (Box 15, Folder 32)
- 1980, Equipment File, 1980-1985; nam_apap209-447 (Box 15, Folder 33)
- 1980, Equipment File, 1980-1985; nam_apap209-448 (Box 15, Folder 34)
- 1980, Equipment File, Clippings and Vendor Publications, 1980-1985; nam_apap209-449 (Box 15, Folder 35)
- 1980, Inside Albany, Series, 1980-1986; nam_apap209-450 (Box 16, Folder 1-2)
- 1980, I Love New York, Series, 1980-1986; nam_apap209-451 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- 1980, Journal, nam_apap209-452 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- 1980, Keeping P.A.C.E with the New Television, nam_apap209-453 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- 1980, London Trip, nam_apap209-454 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- 1980, Long-Range Planning Committee, 1980-1981; nam_apap209-455 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- 1980, MHCET Financial Statement, nam_apap209-456 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- 1980, NEH Grant Applications, nam_apap209-457 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- 1980, News Clippings on WMHT, nam_apap209-458 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- 1980, Notes on Board Meetings, nam_apap209-459 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- 1980, NPR Memoranda to Station Managers, nam_apap209-460 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- 1980, "NPR or Not? Membership Options", Address, nam_apap209-461 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- 1980, PBS Information Binder (?), nam_apap209-462 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- 1980, PBS Legal Memoranda, Schwartz, Woods, & Miller, nam_apap209-463 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- 1980, PBS Memoranda to Station Managers, nam_apap209-464 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- 1980, PBS Merit Awards, nam_apap209-465 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- 1980, Public Broadcasting, nam_apap209-466 (Box 16, Folder 18-24)
- 1980, Public Broadcasting News, Periodical, 1980 November; nam_apap209-467 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- 1980, The Public Broadcasting Report, Periodical, nam_apap209-468 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- 1980, Public Telecommunications Review, nam_apap209-469 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- 1980, Russell Sage Conference, 1980 October 17; nam_apap209-470 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- 1980, Staff Memoranda, 1980-1986; nam_apap209-471 (Box 16, Folder 29)
- 1980, Spector, Beryl, nam_apap209-472 (Box 16, Folder 30)
- 1980, Television Quarterly, Periodical, Fall 1980; nam_apap209-473 (Box 16, Folder 31)
- 1980, van Rijsewijk, Derk, nam_apap209-474 (Box 16, Folder 32)
- 1980, WMHT Internal Records, nam_apap209-475 (Box 16, Folder 33-40)
- 1980, WMHT Internal Records, 1980-1983; nam_apap209-476 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- 1980, WMHT Procedure Manual, nam_apap209-477 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- 1980, The WMHT Program Guide, nam_apap209-478 (Box 17, Folder 3-4)
- 1980, WMHT Ratings and Surveys, 1980-1987; nam_apap209-479 (Box 17, Folder 5-6)
- 1981, Access, Periodical, nam_apap209-480 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- 1981, Capital Expense Meeting, nam_apap209-481 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- 1981, Corporation for Public Broadcasting (CPB) Five-Year Plan, nam_apap209-482 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- 1981, CPB Publications, nam_apap209-483 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- 1981, CPB Reports, nam_apap209-484 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- 1981, Current, Periodical, nam_apap209-485 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- 1981, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1981 January; nam_apap209-486 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- 1981, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1981 February; nam_apap209-487 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- 1981, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1981 March; nam_apap209-488 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- 1981, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1981 April; nam_apap209-489 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- 1981, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1981 May; nam_apap209-490 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- 1981, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1981 June; nam_apap209-491 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- 1981, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1981 July; nam_apap209-492 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- 1981, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1981 August; nam_apap209-493 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- 1981, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1981 September; nam_apap209-494 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- 1981, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1981 October; nam_apap209-495 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- 1981, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1981 November; nam_apap209-496 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- 1981, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1981 December; nam_apap209-497 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- 1981, Educational and Industrial Television, nam_apap209-498 (Box 17, Folder 25)
- 1981, Endowment Committee, nam_apap209-499 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- 1981, Enhancing Interviewing Skills of Income Maintenance Workers: A Training Manual, SUNY Albany Publication, nam_apap209-500 (Box 17, Folder 27)
- 1981, Grimmer, Jean, nam_apap209-501 (Box 17, Folder 28)
- 1981, The Humanist, Periodical, 1981 September-1981 October; nam_apap209-502 (Box 17, Folder 29)
- 1981, Instructional Television Fixes Service (ITFS), 1981-1984; nam_apap209-503 (Box 17, Folder 30)
- 1981, The MacNeil/Lehrer Report Broadcast Review and Index, nam_apap209-504 (Box 17, Folder 31)
- 1981, News Clippings on WMHT, nam_apap209-505 (Box 17, Folder 32)
- 1981, PBS Underwriting Guidelines, nam_apap209-506 (Box 17, Folder 33)
- 1981, Public Broadcasting, nam_apap209-507 (Box 17, Folder 34-35)
- 1981, Public Broadcasting, nam_apap209-508 (Box 18, Folder 1-6)
- 1981, The Public Broadcasting Report, Periodical, nam_apap209-509 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- 1981, Reaction Line Transcripts, 1981-1986; nam_apap209-510 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- 1981, School of Broadcasting, nam_apap209-511 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- 1981, WAMC, 1981-1986; nam_apap209-512 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- 1981, WARM Application (?), nam_apap209-513 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- 1981, What Broadcasters Should Know About Satellites, Technical Publication, nam_apap209-514 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- 1981, WMHT Development Department, nam_apap209-515 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- 1981, WMHT Internal Records, nam_apap209-516 (Box 18, Folder 14-22)
- 1981, The WMHT Program Guide, Program, nam_apap209-517 (Box 18, Folder 23-24)
- 1981, WMHT Salary Rates, 1981-1986; nam_apap209-518 (Box 18, Folder 25)
- 1982, Access (Periodical), nam_apap209-519 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- 1982, Advertising, 1982-1985; nam_apap209-520 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- 1982, Arbitron Radio Market Reports Description of Methodology, nam_apap209-521 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- 1982, Broadcasting (Periodical), nam_apap209-522 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- 1982, Building Construction, nam_apap209-523 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- 1982, Buying or Building a Broadcast Station (National Association of Broadcasters Report), nam_apap209-524 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- 1982, Channels of Communication, nam_apap209-525 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- 1982, Current (Periodical), nam_apap209-526 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- 1982, Daily Calendar, 1982 November-1983 June; nam_apap209-527 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- 1982, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1982 January; nam_apap209-528 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- 1982, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1982 February; nam_apap209-529 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- 1982, Day-Timer, 1982 March; nam_apap209-530 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- 1982, Day-Timer, nam_apap209-531 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- 1982, Day-Timer, 1982 May; nam_apap209-532 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- 1982, Day-Timer, 1982 June; nam_apap209-533 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- 1982, Day-Timer, 1982 July; nam_apap209-534 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- 1982, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1982 August; nam_apap209-535 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- 1982, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1982 September; nam_apap209-536 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- 1982, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1982 October; nam_apap209-537 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- 1982, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1982 November; nam_apap209-538 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- 1982, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1982 December; nam_apap209-539 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- 1982, Educational and Industrial Television, nam_apap209-540 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- 1982, Endowment Committee, nam_apap209-541 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- 1982, The Independent Film & Video Monthly (Periodical), nam_apap209-542 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- 1982, Journal, nam_apap209-543 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- 1982, Mid-Hudson Transmitter, nam_apap209-544 (Box 19, Folder 26)
- 1982, News Clippings on WMHT, nam_apap209-545 (Box 19, Folder 27)
- 1982, Notebook, nam_apap209-546 (Box 19, Folder 28)
- 1982, PBS Memoranda to Station Managers, nam_apap209-547 (Box 19, Folder 29)
- 1982, PBS National Narrowcast Service, 1982-1984; nam_apap209-548 (Box 19, Folder 30)
- 1982, PBS Underwriting Guidelines, nam_apap209-549 (Box 19, Folder 31)
- 1982, Prospects Committee, 1982-1986; nam_apap209-550 (Box 19, Folder 32)
- 1982, PBS Legal Memoranda (Schwartz, Woods and Miller), nam_apap209-551 (Box 19, Folder 33)
- 1982, Public Broadcasting, nam_apap209-552 (Box 19, Folder 34-38)
- 1982, Public Broadcasting news (Periodical), 1982 April; nam_apap209-553 (Box 19, Folder 39)
- 1982, The Public Broadcasting Report (periodical), nam_apap209-554 (Box 19, Folder 40)
- 1982, Schenectady Economic Development Advisory Board, 1982-1984; nam_apap209-555 (Box 19, Folder 41)
- 1982, Schenectady Economic Development Advisory Board, 1982-1984; nam_apap209-556 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- 1982, Shayne, Alan, nam_apap209-557 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- 1982, Staff Registrations, nam_apap209-558 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- 1982, WMHT Internal Records, nam_apap209-559 (Box 20, Folder 4-8)
- 1982, WMHT-FM Internal Records, 1982-1985; nam_apap209-560 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- 1982, WMHT Personnel Committee, nam_apap209-561 (Box 20, Folder 10-11)
- 1982, WMHT Personnel Policy Revisions, nam_apap209-562 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- 1982, The WMHT Program Guide, nam_apap209-563 (Box 20, Folder 13-16)
- 1983, Channels of Communication, nam_apap209-564 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- 1983, CPB Development Newsletter, nam_apap209-565 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- 1983, CPB Publications, nam_apap209-566 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- 1983, Current (periodical), nam_apap209-567 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- 1983, Daily Calendar, 07/1983-12/1983; nam_apap209-568 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- 1983, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1983 January; nam_apap209-569 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- 1983, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1983 February; nam_apap209-570 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- 1983, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1983 March; nam_apap209-571 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- 1983, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1983 April; nam_apap209-572 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- 1983, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1983 May; nam_apap209-573 (Box 20, Folder 26)
- 1983, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1983 June; nam_apap209-574 (Box 20, Folder 27)
- 1983, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1983 July; nam_apap209-575 (Box 20, Folder 28)
- 1983, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1983 August; nam_apap209-576 (Box 20, Folder 29)
- 1983, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1983 September; nam_apap209-577 (Box 20, Folder 30)
- 1983, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1983 October; nam_apap209-578 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- 1983, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1983 November; nam_apap209-579 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- 1983, day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1983 December; nam_apap209-580 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- 1983, Endowment Committee, nam_apap209-581 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- 1983, Exit Interviews, 1983-1986; nam_apap209-582 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- 1983, Finance Committee, nam_apap209-583 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- 1983, Journal, nam_apap209-584 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- 1983, Management, nam_apap209-585 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- 1983, Mexico Trip, nam_apap209-586 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- 1983, Mid-Hudson FM Transmitter, 1983-1987; nam_apap209-587 (Box 21, Folder 10-11)
- 1983, News Clippings on WMHT, nam_apap209-588 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- 1983, PBS Annual Meeting, nam_apap209-589 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- 1983, PBS FY1984 Planning Budget, nam_apap209-590 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- 1983, PBS Legal Memoranda (Schwartz, Woods and Miller), nam_apap209-591 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- 1983, PBS Memoranda to Station Managers, nam_apap209-592 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- 1983, Public Broadcasting, nam_apap209-593 (Box 21, Folder 17-24)
- 1983, The Public Broadcasting Report, nam_apap209-594 (Box 21, Folder 25)
- 1983, RISE Fifth Anniversary Celebration Program, nam_apap209-595 (Box 21, Folder 26)
- 1983, Schenectady County Grants, 1983-1986; nam_apap209-596 (Box 21, Folder 27)
- 1983. Schwartz, Woods & Miller, 1983-1987; nam_apap209-597 (Box 21, Folder 28)
- 1983, Smoking, nam_apap209-598 (Box 21, Folder 29)
- 1983, State Education Department, 1983-1986; nam_apap209-599 (Box 21, Folder 30)
- 1983, WMHT [Program], nam_apap209-600 (Box 21, Folder 31)
- 1983, WMHT [Program], nam_apap209-601 (Box 22, Folder 1-2)
- 1983, WMHT Finance Committee, 1983-1984; nam_apap209-602 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- 1983, WMHT Internal Records, nam_apap209-603 (Box 22, Folder 4-11)
- 1984, Auction Promotional Poster, nam_apap209-604 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- 1984, Channels of Communication, nam_apap209-605 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- 1984, Communications Director Search, nam_apap209-606 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- 1984, Corporate Support, 1984-1986; nam_apap209-607 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- 1984, County Funding for WMHT, nam_apap209-608 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- 1984, Corporation for Public Broadcasting (CPB) Seminar: "Management Techniques for Chief Executive Officers", nam_apap209-609 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- 1984, CPB Marketing Seminar, nam_apap209-610 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- 1984, Current (Periodical), nam_apap209-611 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- 1984, Daily Calendar, 01/1984-06/1984; nam_apap209-612 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- 1984, Daily-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1984 January; nam_apap209-613 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- 1984, Daily-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1984 February; nam_apap209-614 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- 1984, Daily-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1984 March; nam_apap209-615 (Box 22, Folder 23)
- 1984, Daily-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1984 April; nam_apap209-616 (Box 22, Folder 24)
- 1984, Daily-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1984 May; nam_apap209-617 (Box 22, Folder 25)
- 1984, Daily-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1984 June; nam_apap209-618 (Box 22, Folder 26)
- 1984, Daily-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1984 July; nam_apap209-619 (Box 22, Folder 27)
- 1984, Daily-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1984 August; nam_apap209-620 (Box 22, Folder 28)
- 1984, Daily-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1984 September; nam_apap209-621 (Box 22, Folder 29)
- 1984, Daily-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1984 October; nam_apap209-622 (Box 22, Folder 30)
- 1984, Daily-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1984 November; nam_apap209-623 (Box 22, Folder 31)
- 1984, Daily-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1984 December; nam_apap209-624 (Box 22, Folder 32)
- 1984, EITV, nam_apap209-625 (Box 22, Folder 33)
- 1984, Endowment Committee, nam_apap209-626 (Box 22, Folder 34)
- 1984, Engineering Department, nam_apap209-627 (Box 22, Folder 35)
- 1984, Facilities Guidelines For Public Television Stations, PBS Engineering Report, nam_apap209-628 (Box 22, Folder 36)
- 1984, Federighi, Renie, 1984-1987; nam_apap209-629 (Box 22, Folder 37)
- 1984, Glens Falls Translator, 1984-1986; nam_apap209-630 (Box 22, Folder 38)
- 1984, Grant Writing Seminar, nam_apap209-631 (Box 22, Folder 39)
- 1984, Instructional Television Fixed Services (ITFS), 1984-1987; nam_apap209-632 (Box 22, Folder 40)
- 1984, Johnson, Karen, Mayor of Schenectady, nam_apap209-633 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- 1984, Journal, nam_apap209-634 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- 1984, Management, nam_apap209-635 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- 1984, National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH) Grant Applications, nam_apap209-636 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- 1984, News Clippings on WMHT, nam_apap209-637 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- 1984, Nominating Committee, nam_apap209-638 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- 1984, Nuveen Fund Prospectus, nam_apap209-639 (Box 23, Folder 7-8)
- 1984, PBS Legal Memoranda, Schwartz, Woods, and Miller, nam_apap209-640 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- 1984, PBS Managers' Meeting, nam_apap209-641 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- 1984, PBS Memoranda to Station Managers, nam_apap209-642 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- 1984, Personnel Committee, 1984-1987; nam_apap209-643 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- 1984, Public Broadcasting, nam_apap209-644 (Box 23, Folder 13-25)
- 1984, Public Broadcasting, nam_apap209-645 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- 1984, Public Broadcasting News, Periodical, 1984 May; nam_apap209-646 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- 1984, The Public Broadcasting Report, Periodical, nam_apap209-647 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- 1984, Public Television and Radio and State Governments, nam_apap209-648 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- 1984, Satellite Uplink, 1984-1986; nam_apap209-649 (Box 24, Folder 5-6)
- 1984, State Education Department, 1984-1986; nam_apap209-650 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- 1984, Station Histories, nam_apap209-651 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- 1984, The Teleport Concept, Bound Report on Broadcasting in Erie County, nam_apap209-652 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- 1984, Union, 1984-1986; nam_apap209-653 (Box 24, Folder 10-12)
- 1984, VBI Data Delivery Service, 1984-1985; nam_apap209-654 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- 1984, Westerly, nam_apap209-655 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- 1984, WLIW, 1984-1985; nam_apap209-656 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- 1984, WMHT, Program, nam_apap209-657 (Box 24, Folder 16-17)
- 1984, WMHT Channels, Internal Newsletter, nam_apap209-658 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- 1984, WMHT Internal Records, nam_apap209-659 (Box 24, Folder 19-26)
- 1984, WMHT Internal Records, nam_apap209-660 (Box 25, Folder 1-6)
- 1984, WMHT Internal Records, 1984-1987; nam_apap209-661 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- 1984, WMHT-FM Internal Records, 1984-1986; nam_apap209-662 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- 1984, WMHT Trustees Manual, nam_apap209-663 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- 1984, WUSV Contract, nam_apap209-664 (Box 25, Folder 10-11)
- 1984, WUSV Purchase, 1984-1987; nam_apap209-665 (Box 25, Folder 12-13)
- 1985, Albany County Grant, 1985-1986; nam_apap209-666 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- 1985, Albany Tricentennial, nam_apap209-667 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- 1985, Baruch, Ralph M., nam_apap209-668 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- 1985, Board Directories, 1985-1992; nam_apap209-669 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- 1985, Budget, 1985-1986; nam_apap209-670 (Box 25, Folder 18-19)
- 1985, Capital District Magazine Proposal, nam_apap209-671 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- 1985, Carriage of Public Television By Cable Systems, nam_apap209-672 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- 1985, Channels of Communications, nam_apap209-673 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- 1985, Correspondence, nam_apap209-674 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- 1985, Current (Periodical), nam_apap209-675 (Box 25, Folder 24)
- 1985, Daily Calendar, 1985 July-1985 December; nam_apap209-676 (Box 25, Folder 25)
- 1985, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1985 January; nam_apap209-677 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- 1985, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1985 February; nam_apap209-678 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- 1985, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1985 March; nam_apap209-679 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- 1985, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1985 April; nam_apap209-680 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- 1985, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1985 May; nam_apap209-681 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- 1985, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1985 June; nam_apap209-682 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- 1985, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1985 July; nam_apap209-683 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- 1985, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1985 August; nam_apap209-684 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- 1985, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1985 September; nam_apap209-685 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- 1985, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1985 October; nam_apap209-686 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- 1985, Day-Timer, 1985 November; nam_apap209-687 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- 1985, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1985 November; nam_apap209-688 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- 1985, Day-Timer and Travel Expenses, 1985 December; nam_apap209-689 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- 1985, Development, nam_apap209-690 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- 1985, EITV, nam_apap209-691 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- 1985, Endowment Committee, nam_apap209-692 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- 1985, Engineering Department, nam_apap209-693 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- 1985, Environmental Clearinghouse of Schenectady (ECOS), nam_apap209-694 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- 1985, Fiscal Fitness, WMHT Production, Transcript, nam_apap209-695 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- 1985, Instructional Television Fixed Service (ITFS), nam_apap209-696 (Box 26, Folder 20)
- 1985, Journal, nam_apap209-697 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  (includes inserts).
- 1985, KCSD, Kansas City, Information Packet, nam_apap209-698 (Box 26, Folder 22)
- 1985, KUHT, nam_apap209-699 (Box 26, Folder 23)
- 1985, Land Mobile Uplink, 1985-1986; nam_apap209-700 (Box 26, Folder 24)
- 1985, Legislation Affecting Public Broadcasting, 1985-1986; nam_apap209-701 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- 1985, News Clippings on WMHT, nam_apap209-702 (Box 26, Folder 26)
- 1985, News Service, nam_apap209-703 (Box 26, Folder 27)
- 1985, Nielsen Ratings, nam_apap209-704 (Box 26, Folder 28)
- 1985, NTIA Grant Proposal, nam_apap209-705 (Box 26, Folder 29)
- 1985, PBS Anti-Clutter Survey, nam_apap209-706 (Box 26, Folder 30)
- 1985, PBS National Advertising Plan, 1985-1986; nam_apap209-707 (Box 26, Folder 31)
- 1985, PBS Program Duplication Policies, nam_apap209-708 (Box 26, Folder 32)
- 1985, Public Broadcasting, nam_apap209-709 (Box 26, Folder 33-39)
- 1985, Public Broadcasting, nam_apap209-710 (Box 27, Folder 1-9)
- 1985, The Public Broadcasting Report, Periodical, nam_apap209-711 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- 1985, Public Citizen, Periodical, nam_apap209-712 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- 1985, RPI Course in Technical Writing, nam_apap209-713 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- 1985, Satellite Uplink, nam_apap209-714 (Box 27, Folder 13-15)
- 1985, Satellite Uplink, NTIA Endorsement, nam_apap209-715 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- 1985, SCC Human Relations Seminar, nam_apap209-716 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- 1985, "Sharing Savings" Bonus, nam_apap209-717 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- 1985, Staff Directories, 1985-1991; nam_apap209-718 (Box 27, Folder 19)
- 1985, Television/Broadcast Communications, Periodical, nam_apap209-719 (Box 27, Folder 20)
- 1985, Williams, Bon, Computer Consultant, nam_apap209-720 (Box 27, Folder 21)
- 1985, WMHT, Program, nam_apap209-721 (Box 27, Folder 22-23)
- 1985, WMHT Capital Planning Schedule, nam_apap209-722 (Box 27, Folder 24)
- 1985, WMHT Internal Records, nam_apap209-723 (Box 27, Folder 25-27)
- 1985, WMHT Internal Records, nam_apap209-724 (Box 28, Folder 1-8)
- 1986, A Tribal Memory of Public Broadcasting, CPB Report, nam_apap209-725 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- 1986, Auction, nam_apap209-726 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- 1986, Board of Trustees, nam_apap209-727 (Box 28, Folder 11-12)
- 1986, Boy Scout Explorers, 1986-1987; nam_apap209-728 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- 1986, Capital Drive, nam_apap209-729 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- 1986, Capital Fund Drive Consultants, nam_apap209-730 (Box 28, Folder 15-16)